MICHAEL HERRING

206 Kotara Canyon San Antonio TX, 78260 · (210) 284-1082 m.herring11@yahoo.com

Seeking a stable and challenging position in a growth oriented progressive company where my experience and skills will significantly contribute to the overall success of the organization and provide opportunities for my career growth. Resourceful Senior Field Technician with over 6 years of Oil & Gas experience. A hands-on individual with proven skills in troubleshooting, diagnosing field related problems, and maintaining equipment. With a focus on developing and maintaining customer relationships.

EXPERIENCE

03/2020 - PRESENT DELIVERY DRIVER, techline pipe

- Responsible for driving and delivering pre-ordered pipe and material to assigned accounts
- Maintain truck operations and DOT readiness
- Help plan more efficient routes and delivery of material
- Check accuracy and stability of load to ensure safety
- Build strong relationships with clients

07/2014 - 09/2019

SENIOR FIELD SERVICE TECHNICIAN, MULTI-CHEM

- Collect critical customer information to improve customer relationship.
- Perform oil and water testing to diagnose any issues
- Routinely collect oilfield samples and analyze data to present to customers
- Set-up and label storage tanks and containment
- Perform and execute all testing within the lab setting
- Pull and accurately read and record gas tubes.
- · Efficient at grinding out oil samples.
- Familiar with and knowledgeable on fluid separation equipment.
- Properly maintain, operate and repair all company equipment required for performing job duties
- Provide excellent customer service skills with all customers and field office personnel
- Maintain the highest level of safety at all times
- Works well independently and in a team atmosphere

04/2013 - 06/2014

FRAC EQUIPEMENT OPERATOR, SCHLUMBERGER

- Operate equipment and pump unit while maintaining excellent quality control in accordance with company policies
- Spot equipment into position for rigging up and also for rigging down.
- Comply with all government regulations, industry standards and observe all health and safety policies
- Developed a working knowledge of the major components of pumping equipment
- Properly maintain, operate and repair all company equipment required for performing job duties

05/2008 - 3/2013

PERSONAL TRAINER, GOLD'S GYM

- Planned and instructed individuals, small groups or classes with a personalized approach
- Contacted members on a regular basis to follow up on progress of their fitness program
- Maintain accurate records of members progress
- Ensure safe and effective workouts and workout plans
- · Build strong relationships with clients

EDUCATION

DECEMBER 2003

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS, TEXAS TECH UNIVERSITY

NO DEGREE

AUGUST 2001

INFORMATION SYSTEMS, MARY HARDIN BAYLOR UNIVERSITY

NO DEGREE

MAY 2001 JAMES MADISON HIGH SCHOOL HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

- H2S
- CPR/AED
- PEC

- Respirator Fit Test
- CDL class A
- HAZMAT/TANKERS endorsement

REFERENCES

Chris Hall (210) 473-2720 Financial advisor - Pontem Financial

Doug Archer – (210) 776-6117